[{"answer": "I asked you if you're ok", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I don't know. You're not my patient", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Then don't", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What about my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Well, where are you from", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Of course you don't know", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I'm not sure.  I don't really know", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Why", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " I do it", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "No. I used to be a nurse", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "He's got his gun pointed at a kid", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yeah, well, none of this is our fuckin' problem", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " You sure he wasn't provoked", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I'm sure he took some, too", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Happens sometimes when you've got to restrain them. You watch the rest of us work. You know that", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Yes, they are", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "We were forced to use restrains if that's what you're referring to", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Actually, that's exactly what our equipment is", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "They found my friend' body dead in the snow", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I don't know. But he did die", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "That conviction doesn't convince me of anything. Until I know that I did it, I'm not going to accept that I did", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No. The real events that have happened to me have been fucked up. Not my mind", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "The Organization...for the Organized", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No, Mr. my friend. I have not", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "He just said...that I'd shock my friend and then things would change for him", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I still don't either, even after all these years", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "It's important for you to know who your father was, isn't it", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "It's almost as if your life depended on it. Isn't it", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Then help me understand. You know, you're not alone. A lot of Gulf Vets have begun to experience curious symptoms. What you have might well be a syndrome and, if so, it's not one we know enough about to be treating it this vigorously", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Then what? What?  I can't guess it. You have to help me", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Ok fine. Tell me about it. Tell me about the future. 2004. What does it look like", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "The future doesn't look different", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "NO! They're not my delusions! Look, just leave my business with my friend to me", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "One's got everything to do with the other. So unless you want my blood on your hands...leave what's between me and my friend between me and my friend", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Of course not.  I swear I haven't. I wouldn't do that to my friend, or you. You know that", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "No. I would have told you", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "You died, my friend. Years ago, in the hospital", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "No. I didn't. I swear I didn't. I probably helped push you to kill yourself, but I didn't do it", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I'm in it as we speak.  You're haunting yourself right now.  I guess sometimes we indict ourselves if no one else does. You didn't make history like you wanted to, huh, Dr. my friend. It turned out different, didn't it", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "No.  You put me on drugs and then you put me in the Jacket", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Would you like anything, Dr. my friend", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Is he gonna be ok", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "I'm not gonna let that happen", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I do believe you..", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Hi", "docId": "The_Jacket.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I remember you, too", "qsentId": 46}]